{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Mobile Systems and Technologies",
    "Term": "Finals",
    "Title": "SQLite Databases",
    "LastModified": "08 May 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "05 Handout 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "Where is the source code for SQLite located?",
      "answer": "Public Domain",
      "choices": [
        "Public Domain",
        "Proprietary Domain",
        "Domain Expansion: Malevolent Kitchen",
        "Private Domain"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1",
      "term": "Pre-finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following qualities imply that SQLite requires NO other components?",
      "answer": "Self-contained",
      "choices": [
        "Serverless",
        "Zero-configuration",
        "Self-contained",
        "Transactional"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1",
      "term": "Pre-finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "SQLite is written in what language?",
      "answer": "C",
      "choices": [
        "C++",
        "Java",
        "C#",
        "C"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1",
      "term": "Pre-finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What method runs the provided SQL and returns a Cursor of the result set.",
      "answer": "rawQuery()",
      "choices": [
        "tableQuery()",
        "rawQuery()",
        "selectQuery()",
        "cursorQuery()"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1",
      "term": "Pre-finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "SQLite requires a separate server process to run.",
      "answer": "False",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "Maybe",
        "False",
        "A secret other option"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1",
      "term": "Pre-finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What SQLite method opens a database if it exists or create one if it doesn't yet?",
      "answer": "openOrCreateDatabase()",
      "choices": [
        "openOrCreateDatabase()",
        "createOrOpenDatabase()",
        "accessDatabase()",
        "selectDatabase()"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1",
      "term": "Pre-finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a cursor?",
      "answer": "A pointer to a table row",
      "choices": [
        "Where editing takes place",
        "The arrow on the screen",
        "The result set from a rawQuery() method call",
        "A pointer to a table row"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1",
      "term": "Pre-finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What class has methods to execute SQL commands and perform other common database management tasks?",
      "answer": "SQLiteDatabase",
      "choices": [
        "SQLiteDatabase",
        "SQLitePackage",
        "SQLiteDB",
        "SQLiteDBMS"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1",
      "term": "Pre-finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among these is NOT a characteristic of a SQL database engine?",
      "answer": "Efficient",
      "choices": [
        "Self-contained",
        "Zero-configuration",
        "Efficient",
        "Transactional"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1",
      "term": "Pre-finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What SQLite method executes an SQL statement?",
      "answer": "execSQL()",
      "choices": [
        "execSQL()",
        "executeSQL()",
        "execute()",
        "doSQL()"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1",
      "term": "Pre-finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "BONUS: Wha haffen vella?",
      "answer": "Why you crying again?",
      "choices": [
        "Vamfire will feyt to me!",
        "Why you crying again?",
        "I know, vamfire ryt?",
        "Pinagsasabi mo teh"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1",
      "term": "Pre-finals"
    }
  ]
}